<DOC> <DOCNO> 1 </DOCNO> Homepage Accessibility links Skip to content Accessibility Help    BBC Account require(['idcta/statusbar'], function (statusbar) {new statusbar.Statusbar({id: 'idcta-statusbar', publiclyCacheable: true});}); Notifications     Home News Sport Weather iPlayer Sounds CBBC CBeebies Food Bitesize Arts Taster Local Three Menu    Search Search the BBC Search the BBC      
 

 BBC News News Navigation Sections Home Home selected Coronavirus Video World Asia UK Business Tech Science Stories Entertainment  & Arts Health World News TV In Pictures Reality Check Newsbeat Long Reads More  More sections Home Home selected Coronavirus Coronavirus Home Your Coronavirus Stories Video World World Home Africa Australia Europe Latin America Middle East US  & Canada Asia Asia Home China India UK UK Home England N. Ireland Scotland Wales Local News Business Business Home Market Data New Economy New Tech Economy Companies Entrepreneurship Technology of Business Business of Sport Global Education Economy Global Car Industry Tech Science Stories Entertainment  & Arts Health Health Home Coronavirus World News TV In Pictures Reality Check Newsbeat Long Reads 

 
 BBC News Home 
 Breaking Breaking news Close breaking news 
 Latest Stories Most Read Skip to most read Latest Stories Most Read 
 
 

 
 Top Stories India begins world 's biggest Covid vaccine drive Health and frontline workers are first in line for jabs at vaccination centres across the country. 11h 11 hours ago India India begins world 's biggest Covid vaccine drive Health and frontline workers are first in line for jabs at vaccination centres across the country. 11h 11 hours ago India Related content How India is readying for its massive vaccine drive Can the world 's largest vaccine maker meet demand? How do you vaccinate a billion people? Uganda 's Yoweri Museveni declared election winner But his main rival Bobi Wine claims vote-rigging and vows to produce evidence. 7m 7 minutes ago Africa Nepali climbers make history with K2 winter summit Till now, K2 was the only mountain higher than 8,000m not to be conquered in winter. 18m 18 minutes ago Asia All 50 US states on alert for armed protests National Guard troops from across the country descend on Washington DC amid tightened security. 3h 3 hours ago US  & Canada Volcano spews ash above Indonesia 's Java island Mount Semeru has erupted, pouring volcanic matter miles into the air and placing locals on alert. 1h 37 minutes ago Asia Protect us from unlawful killing charges - medics UK health groups say NHS staff fear prosecution over decisions if hospitals are overwhelmed. 4h 4 hours ago UK Video 3 minutes 58 seconds Video 3 minutes 58 seconds 3:58 Video 3 minutes 58 seconds What does the world want from Joe Biden? We speak to reporters in six global regions about hopes and expectations for the new US administration. 18h 18 hours ago US  & Canada Tennis stars ' arrival angers stranded Australians Players are flown in ahead of the Australian Open while thousands of citizens are waiting to return. 3h 3 hours ago Australia Nasa 's  'megarocket ' set to fire up engines The four main engines for Nasa 's new  "megarocket " are to be fired in unison for the first time. 8h 8 hours ago Science  & Environment Centrist elected leader of Merkel 's CDU party Centrist Armin Laschet is now in a good position to succeed Angela Merkel as Germany 's chancellor. 6h 6 hours ago Europe Final execution of Trump presidency is carried out The execution of Dustin Higgs, 48, is the 13th federal death sentence carried out since July. 9h 9 hours ago US  & Canada Centrist elected leader of Merkel 's CDU party Centrist Armin Laschet is now in a good position to succeed Angela Merkel as Germany 's chancellor. 6h 6 hours ago Europe Final execution of Trump presidency is carried out The execution of Dustin Higgs, 48, is the 13th federal death sentence carried out since July. 9h 9 hours ago US  & Canada US expects  'rapid growth ' of virus variant Health officials warn the highly contagious UK Covid variant could become the dominant strain in the US by March. 15h 15 hours ago US  & Canada Dozens dead as Indonesia quake flattens hospital The earthquake struck the island of Sulawesi on Friday, injuring hundreds and destroying a hospital. 20h 20 hours ago Asia Video 2 minutes 54 seconds Video 2 minutes 54 seconds 2:54 Video 2 minutes 54 seconds Four-year-old 's viral dinosaur song made into book Dinosaurs In Love went viral last year. Musician Tom Rosenthal and his daughter Fenn were the ones behind it. 18h 18 hours ago Entertainment  & Arts 
 
 
 
 
 Must See Video Video Spacing out and a famous frozen waterfall How to Watch BBC World News TV The latest global news, sport, weather and documentaries Audio Listen Live Audio BBC World Service Radio Stories from around the world Video Video The surveillance of Martin Luther King Jr Global Covid death toll reaches two million  Video Video One girl 's quest for clean water Critics welcome  'delightful ' WandaVision Striking news pictures from around the world 
 Most watched 1 Video What does the world want from Joe Biden? 2 Video Four-year-old 's viral dinosaur song made into book 3 Video Inside the world 's richest e-sports player 's mansion 4 Video The surveillance of Martin Luther King Jr 5 Video One girl 's quest for clean water 
 Full Story See All End to Gibraltar land border prompts joy and trepidation 'Like a medieval battle ': The riots frontline How worrying are the new coronavirus variants? Pressure and propaganda - the reality of reporting Xinjiang At the Capitol: Trump 's Christian supporters Why a teacher was killed  'execution-style ' in Ethiopia BBC Future: How effective is a single vaccine dose? 
 
 In case you missed it See All 'Broken eggshell ' that left young Chinese homeless Smart locks: Convenience comes with security doubts Video Video 'If helping people is seditious then I am guilty ' The stateless man who set himself alight Can Pakistan protect its religious minorities? 
 Most read 1 All 50 US states on alert for armed protests 2 Uganda 's Yoweri Museveni declared election winner 3 The 69-year-old trolled for her  'too sexy ' photos 4 Protect us from unlawful killing charges - medics 5 Nepali climbers make history with K2 winter summit 6 Tennis stars ' arrival angers stranded Australians 7 Final execution of Trump presidency is carried out 8 Volcano spews ash above Indonesia 's Java island 9 When will Trump go on trial in the Senate? 10 Nasa 's  'megarocket ' set to fire up engines 
 Around the BBC Where we are on climate in five charts BBC Future The  'micro-assault ' of mispronunciation BBC Worklife The erotic design of Italian pastries BBC Travel The most disastrous biopics ever made BBC Culture How much of your body is actually you? BBC Earth How effective is a single vaccine dose? BBC Future The habit that quiets self-criticism BBC Worklife 
 
 
 
 
 Sport See All Live Live Premier League: Robinson red card for Fulham against Chelsea Football 'Sri Lanka exposed England 's weaknesses ' - former captain Vaughan 4h 4 hours ago Cricket Brighton end winless run with victory at Leeds 3m 3 minutes ago Football  Comments Australia remain on top in decisive Test with India 10h 10 hours ago Cricket  Comments Antonio strike gives West Ham win over lacklustre Burnley 1h an hour ago Football  Comments Arsenal 's Ozil close to Fenerbahce move 4h 4 hours ago Football Nearly 50 players have to quarantine in Melbourne hotel rooms 2h 2 hours ago Tennis 
 Find us here News daily newsletter Get news from the BBC in your inbox each weekday morning Mobile app Find out more about our BBC News App Get in touch Email us at  haveyoursay@bbc.co.uk Send an SMS or MMS to  +44 7624 800100 Follow  Have Your Say on Twitter Why you can trust BBC News 
 News Navigation Sections Sections Home Home selected Coronavirus Coronavirus Home Your Coronavirus Stories Video World World Home Africa Australia Europe Latin America Middle East US  & Canada Asia Asia Home China India UK UK Home England N. Ireland Scotland Wales Local News Business Business Home Market Data New Economy New Tech Economy Companies Entrepreneurship Technology of Business Business of Sport Global Education Economy Global Car Industry Tech Science Stories Entertainment  & Arts Health Health Home Coronavirus World News TV In Pictures Reality Check Newsbeat Long Reads 
 
 
 
 


     !function(){var a=!0;if("object"==typeof bbccookies&&"function"==typeof bbccookies.readPolicy&&(a=!bbccookies.readPolicy().performance),a&&-1!==document.cookie.indexOf("_chartbeat"))for(var b=document.cookie.split(";"),c=b.length;c--;){var d=b[c].replace(/^\s+|\s+$/g,""),e=d.split("=")[0];0===e.indexOf("_chartbeat")&&(document.cookie=e+"=; expires=Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 GMT; path=/;")}_sf_async_config.noCookies=a}(),function(){function a(){window._sf_endpt=(new Date).getTime();var a=document.createElement("script");a.setAttribute("language","javascript"),a.setAttribute("type","text/javascript"),a.setAttribute("src","//static.chartbeat.com/js/chartbeat.js"),document.body.appendChild(a)}var b=window.onload;window.onload="function"!=typeof window.onload?a:function(){b(),a()}}(); 
 require.config({"paths":{"bump-3":"//emp.bbci.co.uk/emp/bump-3/bump-3","bump-4":"//emp.bbci.co.uk/emp/bump-4/bump-4","echo-8.1.0":"//static.bbci.co.uk/echoclient/modules/echo-8.1.0.js","jssignals-1":"//static.bbci.co.uk/frameworks/jssignals/0.3.6/modules/jssignals-1","jquery-1":"//static.test.bbc.co.uk/frameworks/jquery/0.4.1/sharedmodules/jquery-1.7.2","jquery-1.9":"//static.bbci.co.uk/frameworks/jquery/0.4.1/sharedmodules/jquery-1.9.1","swfobject-2":"//static.bbci.co.uk/frameworks/swfobject/0.1.10/sharedmodules/swfobject-2","istats-1":"//nav.files.bbci.co.uk/orbit-webmodules/0.0.2-524.9a574c9/istats/istats-1"}}) 
 /* eslint-disable no-unused-expressions, init-declarations, eol-last, semi */

(function (pathToEnhancedJavascript) {
    var my, script;

    if (window.location.search.indexOf('morph-disable-enhanced=1') < 0) {
        my = document.getElementById('nw-c-navigation-enhanced-javascript');

        script = document.createElement('script');
        script.type = 'text/javascript';
        script.src = pathToEnhancedJavascript;
        script.async = true;
        script.defer = true;

        my.parentNode.insertBefore(script, my.nextSibling);
    }
})('//m.files.bbci.co.uk/modules/bbc-morph-news-navigation-body/6.0.1/navigation.js'); 
 
   /*<![CDATA[*/
        require(['orb/nav'], function(nav) {
            window.bbcuser.isUKCombined().then(function(isUK) {
                if (isUK) {
                    nav.loadJs('https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/orbit/1006e027378d380307cb073290531b27/js/edr.min.js');
                }
            });
        });
        /*]]>*/   Explore the BBC Home News Sport Weather iPlayer Sounds CBBC CBeebies Food Bitesize Arts Taster Local Three window.orb.worldwideFooterlinks = '<li class="orb-footer-ads"><a href="https://www.bbcglobalnews.com/">Advertise with us<' + '/a><' + '/li><li class="orb-footer-adchoices"><a href="https://www.bbc.com/usingthebbc/cookies/how-can-i-change-my-bbc-cookie-settings/">AdChoices / Do Not Sell My Info<' + '/a><' + '/li>'; Terms of Use About the BBC Privacy Policy Cookies Accessibility Help Parental Guidance Contact the BBC Get Personalised Newsletters Copyright  © 2021 BBC.  The BBC is not responsible for the content of external sites.  Read about our approach to external linking.    require.config({
            paths: {
                "mybbc/templates": '//mybbc.files.bbci.co.uk/notification-ui/4.2.9/templates',
                "mybbc/notifications": '//mybbc.files.bbci.co.uk/notification-ui/4.2.9/js'
            }
        });

        require(['mybbc/notifications/NotificationsMain', 'idcta/idcta-1'], function (NotificationsMain, idcta) {

            var loadNotifications = function (isUK) {
                if (isUK) {
                    window.bbcpage.loadCSS('//mybbc.files.bbci.co.uk/notification-ui/4.2.9/css/main.min.css').then(function() {
                        NotificationsMain.run(idcta, '//mybbc.files.bbci.co.uk/notification-ui/4.2.9/');
                    });
                }
            };
            
            window.bbcuser.isUKCombined().then(function(isUK) {
                loadNotifications(isUK);
            });
        });       if (window.SEARCHBOX.locale) {
    require.config({
      paths: {
        "search/searchbox": window.SEARCHBOX.searchboxAppStaticPrefix,
      }
    });

    if (bbcuser && bbcuser.isUKCombined) {
        bbcuser.isUKCombined().then(function (isUK) {
            if (isUK) {
                require(['search/searchbox/searchboxDrawer'], function (SearchboxDrawer) {
                  SearchboxDrawer.run(window.SEARCHBOX);
                });
            }
        });
    }

  }       require.config({
    "paths": {
        "orb/async/_footerpromo": 'https://nav.files.bbci.co.uk/navpromo/540f3f6dbf28b119bbe06e61544e3f22/js/async/_footerpromo'
    }
});
(function() {


    document.addEventListener("DOMContentLoaded", function(event) {
      initialiseFooter();
    });

    var scrollCheckTimer;
    var didScroll;
    var previousPosition = 0;
    var delta = 5;
    var PROMO_SHOW_BREAKPOINT = 1500;
    var pageLength = 0;

    function getCookie(key) {
        if (!key) {
            return document.cookie;
        }
        return decodeURIComponent(document.cookie.replace(new RegExp("(?:(?:^|.*;)\\s*" + encodeURIComponent(key).replace(/[\-\.\+\*]/g, "\\$&") + "\\s*\\=\\s*([^;]*).*$)|^.*$"), "$1")) || null;
    }

    function initialiseFooter() {
        // Suppress this feature on browsers we no longer test
        var myNav = navigator.userAgent.toLowerCase();
        var oldIE = (myNav.indexOf('msie') !== -1) && parseInt(myNav.split('msie')[1], 10) <= 10;
        if (!oldIE) {
            var disabledByCookie = (parseInt(getCookie('ckns_nav_promofail')) || 0) >= 3;
            if (!disabledByCookie) {
                window.bbcpage.getLanguage().then(function(language) {
                    if (language === 'en') {
                        window.bbcuser.isUKCombined().then(function(isUK) {
                            if (isUK) {
                                setUpLazyLoading();
                            }
                        });
                    }
                });
            }
        }
    }

    function setUpLazyLoading() {
        // offsetHeight is expensive to calculate, only do it once.
        pageLength = Math.abs(document.body.offsetHeight);

        if (pageLength < getViewportHeight() + 300 || pageLength - getCurrentPosition() < PROMO_SHOW_BREAKPOINT) {
            loadPromo();

        } else {
            window.onscroll = function () {
                didScroll = true;
            };

            scrollCheckTimer = setInterval(function () {
                if (didScroll) {
                    hasScrolled();
                    didScroll = false;
                }
            }, 250);
        }
    }

    function loadPromo() {
        clearInterval(scrollCheckTimer);

        require(['orb/async/_footerpromo'], function(promo) {
            promo.init('https://navpromo.api.bbci.co.uk', '');
        });
    }

    function getViewportHeight() {
        return window.innerHeight;
    }

    function getCurrentPosition() {
        return Math.abs(window.scrollY || document.body.scrollTop || document.documentElement.scrollTop);
    }

    function hasScrolled() {
        var currentPosition = getCurrentPosition();

        if (Math.abs(previousPosition - currentPosition) <= delta) {
            return;
        }
        if (currentPosition > previousPosition) {
            if ((pageLength - currentPosition) <= PROMO_SHOW_BREAKPOINT) {
                loadPromo();
            }
        }
        previousPosition = currentPosition;
    }
})();      window.COOKIES_STATIC_HOST = 'https://nav.files.bbci.co.uk/orbit-webmodules/0.0.2-562.3a038b3/cookie-banner/cookie-prompt/';    "use strict";window.__reverb.__reverbLoadedPromise.then(function(e){return e.initialise().then(function(){return e.viewEvent()})},function(){console.log("Failed to load reverb. No event sent")}); </DOC>
